{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which of the following database activities allow for the actual retrieval and use of a database?", "opta": "Enterprise modeling", "optb": "Logical database design", "optc": "Physical database design and definition", "optd": "Database implementation", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The three-schema components include all, but:", "opta": "internal schema.", "optb": "conceptual schema.", "optc": "programming schema.", "optd": "external schema.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is not a type of data management technology?", "opta": "Relational", "optb": "Rational", "optc": "Object-oriented", "optd": "Dimensional", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is not a relevant feature of CASE tools?", "opta": "The ability to help draw data models using entity-relationship notations", "optb": "The ability to generate code", "optc": "An information repository", "optd": "Access to a DB via the Internet", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The first step in database development is which of the following?", "opta": "Enterprise data modeling", "optb": "Logical database design", "optc": "Physical database design and definition", "optd": "Database Implementation", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following database activities determines the entities, attributes, and relationships of data?", "opta": "Conceptual data modeling", "optb": "Logical database design", "optc": "Physical database design and definition", "optd": "Database implementation", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The use of packaged data models can offer which of the following benefits?", "opta": "Reduce implementation time and costs", "optb": "Higher quality models", "optc": "Both A and B.", "optd": "Neither A nor B.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Enterprise tier of the three-tiered database architecture includes:", "opta": "managing the data.", "optb": "managing the User-system interface.", "optc": "processing HTTP protocol.", "optd": "processing scripting tasks.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An entity type is which of the following?", "opta": "A major category of data about people, place, and things", "optb": "The various departments of an organization", "optc": "The application software", "optd": "The business processes the support the mission of an organization", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Strategic Planning factors do not include which of the following?", "opta": "Organizational goals", "optb": "Critical success factors", "optc": "Information engineering", "optd": "Problem areas", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CASE tools do not include which of the following features?", "opta": "Help to draw data models", "optb": "Help to generate code", "optc": "Help to manage people", "optd": "Create an information repository", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In enterprise data modeling, which is incorrect?", "opta": "You review current systems.", "optb": "You implement the new database.", "optc": "You describe the data needed at a very high level of abstraction.", "optd": "You plan one or more database development projects.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following database activities require a specific knowledge of a DBMS?", "opta": "Enterprise modeling", "optb": "Conceptual data modeling", "optc": "Logical database design", "optd": "Physical database design and definition", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "User views are included as part of which schema?", "opta": "Internal", "optb": "Conceptual", "optc": "External", "optd": "None of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Whose role is it to determine the requirements and design for a database?", "opta": "Database analysts", "optb": "Database administrators", "optc": "Both A and B.", "optd": "Neither A or B.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}